Good morning.
S-Someone's here! Is...
They're asleep?
That smell... It's Akira-san!
Excuse me... are you...?
That's right. He was
on a stakeout all night.
But why is he sleeping there?!
It's my usual spot,
so I let my guard down!
That was his l-lap...
And I sat right down on it!
I want...
...to kiss more!
Wait, am I just being greedy?!
Maybe people don't
usually do it that often?
If I want to kiss him...
Why don't I just do it?
No one else is here, right?!
Which means now is my chance!
But am I allowed to just do it?
But we're also dating!
J-Just a little one...
There!
This area... around here...
What are you doing?
Um... not telling!
You aren't?
Well, the others don't seem
to have caught on.
Is someone else here?!
No.
W-Were you...
awake this whole time?
Not telling.
Akira-san!
I made copies of
the documents you asked for.
Thank you.
You're in the office
all day today, right?
Yes.
I'm just putting together reports.
Oh, is it that time already?
You can head home if you want.
Thanks for your hard work.
Yes... same to you.
It's been a week since he
brought up living together.
He hasn't even walked me home...
When are we supposed to
discuss the arrangements?!
I'm on tenterhooks about it!
I'm over here searching
for properties online every day!
Is something the matter?
N-No, I just...
wondered if we could
walk home together today.
Let me see...
This could take me a while.
Would you mind waiting?
I-I'll gladly wait!
Oh, that's right.
Since it'll be rather late,
would you be interested
in staying over at my house?
S-Staying over?!
Shizuka-san.
I'm sorry for the long wait.
STAYING OVER
Shizuka-san?
W-We're going to your house, right?!
Ow!
Are you all right?
Should we call it off after all?
Absolutely not!
R-Right.
Anyway,
let's stop by a convenience store to
buy dinner and things you might need.
R-Right!
They have overnight sets
with toner and such.
Is there a brand you prefer?
N-No...
You'll need a makeup remover
and a toothbrush...
The shopping's getting done so fast...
It's so easy!
I don't need to call
over a staff member!
And...
What size bottoms do you wear?
They have M and L.
Emm.
M, right?
I'll get you rung up.
Akira-san is so smooth.
He didn't even hesitate
to ask about my underwear!
Such an adult! Such an adult!
What?
Does that mean...
he's used to this stuff?
W-We're here!
Though, I've actually been here before!
I'm staying... I'm staying
the night tonight!
In a man's apartment...
in my boyfriend's apartment!
Are you nervous?
You seem quite tense.
Since we're considering living
together in the near future,
I thought it would be good
to try a night together...
I guess I am moving too fast, though.
I'm sorry.
That's right!
When you live together,
you spend every night together!
What a thought!
Y-Yes?
Yet I... I...
I totally jumped the gun and started
searching for properties instead!
I'll go home with
Akira-san every day! Squee!
I'm so embarrassed!
I got completely ahead of myself!
She seems extraordinarily anxious.
Er... should we try
the sleepover another night?
I want to try the sleepover.
I don't want to go home.
I understand. Let's spend
the night together.
You must be hungry. Come on in.
Y-Yes! I'm starving!
Oh, I know.
I'd like to show you around my apartment.
What?
You showed me about it
the first time I came...
There are some things
I haven't walked you through yet.
This door is on the right as you enter.
I see.
This is the bedroom.
You usually sleep in here, then?
Yes.
As we walk along
the right side of the bed,
there's a lamp here.
R-Right!
I'll take the couch tonight,
so I want you to stay here.
I'll be sleeping in Akira-san's bed?!
Last, I'll show you to the bath.
Feel free to make use of it now.
I'm naked in Akira-san's house!
But... what is this feeling?
I'm kind of embarrassed,
kind of excited...
Kind of... delighted?
I'm acting like this
over my first sleepover.
Can I really handle this?
Akira-san.
Are you here? I thought
I heard something.
Yes,
I'm sitting on the sofa.
Feel free to sit next to me.
If you don't mind.
Humans dry their hair, don't they?
I'll bring a hair dryer for you.
Invisible people don't have to?
Our hair and skin have different
properties, so we don't need to.
It would actually be bad
for my hair to do so.
I'll get it.
Why does he have one
if he doesn't use it?
If someone stays over? Karma-san, maybe?
He's used to this stuff?
Maybe he had a girlfriend before?
He's so mature and kind, of course,
it's natural that he would...
Here it is.
R-Right!
This should make me so happy...
so why am I anxious?
Did he dry his last
girlfriend's hair like this?
Did he discuss dating with
the presumption of marriage with her?
No, stop that!
Getting in my own head
about it will just depress me!
Did that tickle?
Hey... Akira-san?
I'd like to... kiss.
Let's not.
It might make me want to
skip a few steps.
I'm sorry.
Skip steps to what?!
SKIP A FEW STEPS?!
Well, good night.
Skip steps...
Kissing would make him
want to skip steps and...
Hey.
What's Karma been up to lately?
Haven't seen him around.
Oh, he went back to his shop.
He says he was able to vent a lot of
his curses on that recent investigation.
He said he had to take a page from
Akira-san and focus on his business.
You were awesome back there, Tonome-chan!
I gotta work hard, too!
R-Right.
What's with that guy? Sheesh.
Do you mind if I ask you a question?
What is it?
What led to you and
Madaraito-san living together?
I thought it'd be a question about work.
EARNEST
Efficiency.
That was a very long wait
for a very simple answer!
Don't talk to me about stuff like that.
I guess it's like a work mindset thing.
Detective stuff means extracting
info from someone else,
so I'm guarded about revealing
my personal info to others.
So you're embarrassed?
Shut up. You can't just ask that.
I was just hoping to get some info
for personal reference.
Sorry.
Maybe I'll ask Madaraito-san and—
Don't ask that blabbermouth anything!
The reason we started living
together is because Daichi—
Sorry.
So you guys are gonna
move in together?
Yes!
Yeah, I don't think our experience
is gonna be any help to you.
You don't want practical
advice on cohabiting.
Asking something like that means you've
got something specific on your mind.
Well, that's true...
Tonome-san is just so amazing!
Now you're just bragging.
It's just...
He's too amazing. I keep thinking
I'll end up totally dependent on him...
You think he's too accommodating of you?
Yes! It feels like something like that!
So tell him to stop?
Even though he's amazing?
Speak up or put a stop to it,
and restore some balance.
Though, I can't promise it'll end
up in your ideal form at the end.
I see.
STONE-BAKED SWEET POTATOES
Here you are!
Thank you!
Welcome!
Hello.
Shizuka-san. I brought you back
a baked sweet potato!
I haven't had one in so long!
Can we split it?
Here!
Thank you.
What was that "ah" about?
Do you mind if I check your sweet potato?
Certainly.
I just messed up splitting it.
You...
You took advantage of my blindness!
You rotten SD!
I'm going back to cut it!
S...?
Kikira-san.
What's an SD?
No idea.
Akira-san, I'm sorry.
I was acting really selfishly earlier.
About that...
You've been evaluating me too highly!
Kikira-san told me everything.
SD? Look it up yourself.
Well... I partly want to know
the definition, but...
I was hoping I could talk about it, too...
You're both exhausting.
SD is short for "super darling."
Super...?
In certain circles,
it's used to refer to a desirable,
mature, perpetually smooth, perfect man.
Perfect? Me?
He has an excellent education,
he's tall, he has a good income.
But he's also kind, from a good family,
attractive, and good at housework.
Common SDs with all those
traits include wealthy heirs...
I'm a wealthy heir!
CEOs...
CEO!
And oil barons...
I'm an oil baron!
Shizuka-san,
you shouldn't assume things
just because I'm invisible.
So humble! Amazing!
Am I being too accommodating with you?
I mean...
it's selfish to complain
about you caring about me, right?!
Forget I said anything!
No, it takes courage
to be honest about these things.
Thank you.
No, not at all...
He's even trying
to reassure me... He's so kind...
But it's not because I'm an "SD"
or anything like that.
I want to earn your trust.
Wait.
Hang on... You think I don't trust you?
No, it's nothing like that.
It's more...
Is there a reason it's
hard to talk about?
It's just,
I don't want to make
excuses for my behavior
when you're already feeling anxious...
This is just what I'm talking about!
O-Oh, right. I'm sorry.
For a long time, invisible
people mostly worked as spies
and other secretive professions.
So many of us have few
records of our past,
and don't know our roots.
Our invisibility was considered useful,
but it's hard for us, as a race,
to establish trust with others.
When I was young, too,
I was tutored on how to act.
It was like... Tips about blending
into normal society.
I wonder why that is.
The only thing that makes you different
is that you're invisible, right?
Why does that make it hard
for people to trust you?
The only thing that makes us different?
I guess, from your perspective,
that's not a big difference at all, is it?
I'm really sorry.
Not at all. It makes me happy.
Um...
Does being invisible make life hard
for most invisible people?
A few years back,
an invisible fashion
model appeared on the scene.
He incorporated his
invisibility into his looks
and became the talk of the industry.
It put the existence of invisible
people into the spotlight
and helped people understand us.
Were invisible models really that rare?
I think he was the first
invisible model ever,
though he's retired now.
Meeting him when I was a child saved me.
You know him?!
Yes.
He's part of the reason I started
using clothing to express myself.
He's like a big brother
to me, and a friend.
I didn't know you had
an inspiration like that!
Anyway, I'll try to be a little
less overly accommodating with you.
And I'll start with...
Devouring this donut
right in front of you!
Starting there, hmm?
Another sleepover!
I was nervous at first,
but Akira-san's been acted so normal,
I'm really getting used to it!
And here I was,
hoping for even more
canoodling than before!
What do you mean, even more canoodling?!
Is it kind of a let-down?
It's hard for invisible people
to earn trust with others...
I couldn't tell her the real reason.
I've got to tell her properly sometime.
I really don't want to.
EPISODE 8: I GUESS I'M BEING SELFISH
TO BE CONTINUED